<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our team on NYU Predictive Analytics Unit</title>
    <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our team on NYU Predictive Analytics Unit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Code released under the Apache 2.0 license.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Himanshu Grover</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/himanshu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/himanshu/</guid>
      <description>Himanshu Grover, PhD, is a Data Scientist with PAU. His interests and work lie at the interface of data science and software engineering, focusing on applications in healthcare. As a member of PAU, he applies modern principles and best practices for building robust, performant, scalable systems for analysis and informatics of large-scale clinical data.
Himanshu obtained his MS and PhD degrees in Biomedical Informatics from the University of Pittsburgh. Prior to joining the group, Himanshu was a Postdoctoral Fellow at NYULH, working on designing algorithms and tools for analyzing proteomic mass-spectrometry data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jager Hartman</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/jager/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/jager/</guid>
      <description>Jager is a Data Scientist working on engineering, model improvement, and monitoring.
He received a MS in Data Science from Columbia University and previously a BA in Mathematics and Chemistry from Kalamazoo College.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ji Chen</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/ji/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/ji/</guid>
      <description>Ji Chen, MS, is a PhD student mentored by Yin Aphinyanaphongs. His current research focuses on building personalized clinical decision support tools (CDS) exploiting electronic health record data and machine learning and deep learning techniques.
Ji received his MS in Biology from NYU and his BA in Agronomy from Zhejiang University, China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marina Marin</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/marina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/marina/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Quinn</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/michael/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/michael/</guid>
      <description>Michael Quinn is a Project Manager working with PAU. His interests and work lie in predictive modeling applications within healthcare and efficiency improvements. As a member of both the PAU and MCIT, Michael is responsible for project oversight of research initiatives, as well as ensuring models and healthcare applications are effectively implemented.
Michael is currently pursuing his MS in Epidemiology from Columbia University, with focuses on oncology and specialty pharma. In addition, Michael obtained his BA in Economics from New York University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Narges Razavian</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/narges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/narges/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neil Jethani</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/neil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/neil/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seda Bilaloglu</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/seda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/seda/</guid>
      <description>Seda Bilaloglu, MS, is a Data Scientist/Engineer with PAU interested in clinical machine learning, NLP and neural signal processing.
Seda received an undergraduate degree in Electrical and Electronics Engineering from Bilkent University (Ankara, Turkey), and a Masters degree in Biomedical Engineering from NYU Tandon School of Engineering and is currently pursuing her second Masters in Data Science at NYU. In her spare time, Seda enjoys hiking and discovering NYC with her bike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vincent Major</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/vincent/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/vincent/</guid>
      <description>Vincent Major, ME MS, is a PhD Candidate mentored by Yin Aphinyanaphongs. Since joining NYU in 2015, Vincent has been working with PAU applying machine learning and deep learning techniques to electronic medical record data.
Vincent obtained a MS in Biomedical Informatics from NYU and previously a ME in Bioengineering and a BE(Hons) in Mechanical Engineering from the University of Canterbury, New Zealand. Vincent’s research in New Zealand studied the respiratory dynamics of critical care patients supported by invasive mechanical ventilation using mathematical modeling and signal processing methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walter Wang</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/walter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/walter/</guid>
      <description>Duo (Walter) Wang, MS, is a Solutions Developer at the Center for Healthcare Innovation and Delivery Science. His responsibilities include building and deploying containerized applications for analysis and processing of informatics data. In addition, as a member of Predictive Analytics Unit, he works on leveraging health informatics in the effort to enhance health care delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yin Aphinyanaphongs</title>
      <link>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/yin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nyupau.github.io/docs/team/yin/</guid>
      <description>Yin Aphinyanaphongs, MD, PhD, is an Assistant Professor in the Department of Population Health and Department of Medicine as well as the Director Translational Clinical Informatics for DataCore and the Director of PAU who received his MD and PhD from Vanderbilt University.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>